Guide to the William Singer Moorhead Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
William Singer Moorhead Papers
1935-1988
MS 1490
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
25.17
(55 boxes)
The papers consist of professional correspondence, topical files, legislative files, speeches, writings, and memorabilia which document William Moorhead's career in the House of Representatives from 1958-1980.
Moorhead, William S. (William Singer), 1923-1987
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Lucy G. Moorhead (Mrs. William S.), 1988.
Arrangement
Arranged in four series: I. Correspondence and Topical Files, 1958-1982. II. Legislative Files, 1959-1981. III. Speeches and Writings, 1956-1984. IV. Memorabilia, 1935-1988.
Scope and Contents
The William S. Moorhead Papers consist of professional correspondence, topical files, legislative files, speeches, writings, and memorabilia which document Moorhead's career as the Democratic representative of Pennsylvania's fourteenth congressional district in the House of Representatives from 1958 to 1980. The papers were the gift of Lucy Moorhead in December 1988.
The 21.75 linear feet of papers are arranged in four series:
Series I, CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, consists of alphabetically arranged files containing material which documents Moorhead's professional activities. The majority of the correspondence was generated in response to Moorhead's announcement to retire from public service in 1980 and consists of congratulatory messages and letters of appreciation from constituents and colleagues for Moorhead's support and votes during his eleven terms as a House Democrat.
Moorhead's service on numerous congressional committees and subcommittees and his support and authorship of subsequent legislation are documented by topical files, consisting primarily of printed material, including those detailing the Carnegie-Mellon Bill, the Chrysler Corporation Loan Guarantee Act of 1977, the Energy Security Act, the Intergovernmental Emergency Assistance Act of New York City, the National Foundation of the Arts and Humanities Act, the New York City Financial Assistance Act, and the Urban Development Action Grants (UDAG) of Pennsylvania.
Series II, LEGISLATIVE FILES, is arranged in two sections, "Legislation introduced" and "Remarks in Congressional Record"."Legislation introduced" consists of copies of bills containing legislation which was introduced in the House of Representatives by Moorhead personally or on his behalf. Indices for the congressional sessions providing the title and H. R. number of the bill and its date of introduction are included in the papers. "Remarks in Congressional Record" contains annotated copies/photocopies of remarks made by Moorhead. Indices for the congressional sessions provide the date and subject of the remark and the corresponding page numbers in Congressional Record. A special edition of Congressional Record,"Tributes to Congressman William S. Moorhead of Pennsylvania," was published on the occasion of his retirement and is included in this section.
Newsletters entitled "Congressman William S. Moorhead Reports" and service letters mailed to citizens of the fourteenth congressional district apprising them of local and national legislation are filed at the end of this series.
Series III, SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, consists of speeches presented to civic organizations, academic institutions, and political, professional, youth, and church groups. Indices provide the subject, date, and place of the speeches for each congressional session. Writings files contain articles in draft and/or published form written for various professional publications between 1956 and 1967.
Series IV, MEMORABILIA, consists primarily of files containing awards and certificates, calendars of Moorhead's daily appointments, printed campaign materials of Moorhead and other Democrats, congressional mementoes, photographs documenting his political activities, presidential pens (along with accompanying letters) used to sign legislation sponsored by Moorhead, and scrapbooks of newspaper clippings which trace Moorhead's political life from 1958 until his death in 1987.
There is a minimal amount of personal material in the papers. Series IV does contain Moorhead's diary from 1935, a folder of family photographs, and one folder of personal keepsakes.
dditional files within the series contain materials used by Lucy Galpin Moorhead, wife of William Moorhead, in the writing of Entertaining in Washington.
Oversize materials from Series IV are filed at the end of the papers.
Biographical / Historical
William Singer Moorhead was born in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, on April 8, 1923, the son of a prominent local attorney. He studied at Shady Side Academy in Pittsburgh and at Phillips Academy in Andover, Massachusetts. Moorhead received a Bachelor of Arts degree from Yale University in 1944. Upon graduation, he received a Navy commission as a lieutenant junior grade aboard a destroyer in the Pacific. He served as a combat information center officer and navigator until after the Japanese surrender. He also served in China in 1946 and was released from service later that year. Moorhead graduated cum laude from Harvard Law School in 1949.
Moorhead joined the law firm of Moorhead and Knox founded by his father. He served as assistant city solicitor of Pittsburgh from 1954-1957 and as a member of the Allegheny County Housing Authority from 1956-1958. He participated in the rejuvenation of Pittsburgh inspired by Richard K. Mellon and Mayor David Lawrence.
Moorhead was elected to Congress in 1958 and served as a Democrat for Pennsylvania's fourteenth district in the House of Representatives for twenty-two years. During his eleven terms, from 1958 to 1981, Moorhead served on numerous congressional committees and subcommittees.
In 1964-1965, Moorhead sponsored legislation to create the National Foundation for Arts and Humanities, the forerunner of the National Endowment for the Arts and the National Endowment for the Humanities.
Often referred to as a "watchdog" of government overspending, Moorhead uncovered waste in foreign aid operations, especially in Southeast Asia, in his capacity as chairman of the Subcommittee on Foreign Operations and Government Information. While serving on a subcommittee of the Government Operations Committee, Moorhead revealed cost overruns in the procurement process and in the construction of the C-5A giant transport in particular.
In 1973-1974, Moorhead sponsored amendments to the Freedom of Information and Privacy Acts which allowed the public greater access to government documents and limited government dissemination of information pertaining to citizens.
In response to the OPEC oil embargo of 1973, Moorhead was the chief sponsor of a bill that eventually established a synthetic fuels corporation. The enactment of the Energy Security Act of 1980 was regarded by Moorhead as the capstone of his legislative career, addressing not only the energy needs of the nation, but also the economic interests of western Pennsylvania, which is the home to great stores of coal, the raw material for synthetic fuels.
As chairman of the Economic Stabilization Subcommittee of the Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs Committee, Moorhead presided over the 1978 hearings for federal loan assistance to financially distressed New York City. He initiated federal loan guarantees to rescue New York City and the Chrysler Corporation from bankruptcy, despite critics' fears of setting the precedent for government bailouts.
Moorhead retired from the House in 1981 rather than run for a twelfth term. He joined the law firm of Coan, Couture, Lyons and Moorhead in Washington.
William S. Moorhead died on August 3, 1987, of lung cancer at Johns Hopkins Hospital, Baltimore. He is survived by his wife, formerly Lucy Galpin; a daughter, Perrin Moorhead Grayson; and three sons, William S. III, Stephen G., and James B. Moorhead.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Finance, Public -- New York (State) -- New York; New York (N.Y.); Legislators; Moorhead, William S. (William Singer), 1923-1987; United States. Congress. House; Chrysler Corporation; National Endowment for the Arts; National Endowment for the Humanities
- CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, 1958-1982; Series I; 1.5 linear feet (4 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence and topical files arranged alphabetically by subject name. Within the files, correspondence and printed materials are arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1958, 1962, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Letters of appreciation for Moorhead's support/votes, 1979 March-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Retirement: congratulatory messages with Moorhead's responses
      - Congress members, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Non-Pennsylvanians, 1980 January-1981 December (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
      - Pennsylvanians, 1980 January-1980 December (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
      - Requests for support of congressional campaign of son, William S. Moorhead, III, 1980 January-1980 March (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
      - Luncheon sponsored by Pennsylvania congressional delegation, 1980 September (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Form letters, [1980] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Topical files
    - Carnegie-Mellon Bill (H. R. 7385): transfer of certain facilities of the U. S. Bureau of Mines to Carnegie-Mellon University in Pittsburgh
      - Correspondence, printed material, 1959-1974, 1979, 1980 February-July (Box 1, Folder 14-17)
      - Correspondence, printed material, 1980 August-December (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
    - Chrysler Corporation Loan Guarantee Act of 1979 (H. R. 5805)
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee on Economic Stabilization: Part 1A, 1979 October 18-26 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee on Economic Stabilization: Part 1B, 1979 October 30-November 13 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Report of the Committee on Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, 1979 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Findings of the Chrysler Corporation Loan Guarantee Board, 1980 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Report of the Chrysler Corporation Loan Guarantee Board, 1980 July 15 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Public Law 96-185, 1980 January 7 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - 96th Congressional Status Profile, 1979-1980, n. d. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Energy Security Act, S. 932: yea and nay roll call vote, 1980 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Intergovernmental Emergency Assistance Act, New York City, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - National Foundation of the Arts and Humanities Act of 1965, 1965-1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - New York City Financial Assistance Act of 1978
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee on Economic Stabilization: Part 1, 1978 February-March 2 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee on Economic Stabilization: Part 2, 1978 March 7-15 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Report from the Committee on Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs: conference report, 1978 May-July (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Reports to Congress by the U. S. Comptroller General, 1977 April 4 (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
      - New York City Loan Guarantee Act of 1978 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - New York City Loan Program/Seasonal Loan Program, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - New York City Seasonal Financing Act of 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Urban Development Action Grants (UDAG), Pennsylvania
      - Correspondence, printed material, 1979 January-Mar, 1979 June-October (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
      - Parkway Center Mall, Pittsburgh, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Government National Mortgage Association, 1980 April-September (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - William S. Moorhead Federal Building: dedication materials, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- LEGISLATIVE FILES, 1959-1981; Series II; 5.0 linear feet (12 boxes)
  This series contains printed material arranged chronologically within each category. Indices to the legislative files are included.
  - Legislation introduced
    - 86th, 87th Congress: index, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - 86th Congress, 1959 January-1960 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - 87th Congress, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 45-47)
    - 88th Congress: index, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - 88th Congress, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - 89th Congress: index, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - 89th Congress, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 51-52)
    - 90th Congress: index, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - 90th Congress, 1967 January-December (Box 5, Folder 54-56)
    - 90th Congress, 1968 January-1968 June 4, 1968 June 6-October (Box 6, Folder 57-60)
    - 91st Congress, 1st session: index, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - 91st Congress, 1st session, 1969 January-December (Box 6, Folder 62-67)
    - 91st Congress, 2nd session, 1970-December (Box 7, Folder 68-73)
    - 92nd Congress, 1st session: index, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - 92nd Congress, 1st session, 1971 January-February 17, 1971 February 21-December (Box 7, Folder 75-79)
    - 92nd Congress, 2nd session: index, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - 92nd Congress, 2nd session, 1972 January-September 141972 September 18-October (Box 8, Folder 81-84)
    - 93rd Congress, 1st, 2nd sessions: index, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - 93rd Congress, 1st session, 1973 January 3-24, 1973 January 26-April 4, 1973 April-July (Box 8, Folder 86-90)
    - 93rd Congress, 1st session, 1973 August-December (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - 93rd Congress, 2nd session: index, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - 93rd Congress, 2nd session, 1974 January-December (Box 9, Folder 93-96)
    - 94th Congress, 1st, 2nd sessions: index, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - 94th Congress, 1st session, 1975 January-February 10, 1975 February 19-March 10, 1975 March 14-June (Box 9, Folder 98-101)
    - 94th Congress, 1st session, 1975 July-December (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - 94th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - 94th Congress, 2nd session, 1976 January-October (Box 10, Folder 104-106)
    - 95th Congress, 1st session: index, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - 95th Congress, 1st session, 1977 January-December (Box 10, Folder 108-111)
    - 95th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - 95th Congress, 2nd session, 1978 January-October (Box 11, Folder 113-116)
    - 96th Congress, 1st session: index, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - 96th Congress, 1st session, 1979 January-December (Box 11, Folder 118-121)
    - 96th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - 96th Congress, 2nd session, 1980 January-December (Box 12, Folder 123-126)
    - Remarks in Congressional Record
      - 86th Congress, 1st session: index, 1959 January-September (Box 12, Folder 127)
      - 86th Congress, 1st session, 1959 January-October (Box 12, Folder 128)
      - 86th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1960 January-June (Box 12, Folder 129)
      - 86th Congress, 2nd session, 1960 January-June (Box 12, Folder 130)
      - 87th Congress, 1st session: index, 1961 January-September (Box 12, Folder 131)
      - 87th Congress, 1st session, 1961 January-September (Box 12, Folder 132)
      - 87th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1962 January-October (Box 12, Folder 133)
      - 87th Congress, 2nd session, 1962 January-October (Box 12, Folder 134)
      - 88th Congress, 1st session: index, 1963 January-December (Box 12, Folder 135)
      - 88th Congress, 1st session, 1963 January-December (Box 12, Folder 136-138)
      - 88th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1964 January-October (Box 12, Folder 139)
      - 88th Congress, 2nd session, 1964 January-October (Box 13, Folder 140-141)
      - 89th Congress, 1st session: index, 1965 January-October (Box 13, Folder 142)
      - 89th Congress, 1st session, 1965 January-October (Box 13, Folder 143-145)
      - 89th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1966 January-November (Box 13, Folder 146)
      - 89th Congress, 2nd session, 1966 January-November (Box 13, Folder 147-149)
      - 90th Congress, 1st session: index, 1967 January-December (Box 13, Folder 150)
      - 90th Congress, 1st session, 1967 January-December (Box 13, Folder 151-154)
      - 90th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1968 January-October (Box 13, Folder 155)
      - 90th Congress, 2nd session, 1968 January-October (Box 13, Folder 156-158)
      - 91st Congress, 1st session: index, 1969 January-December (Box 14, Folder 159)
      - 91st Congress, 1st session, 1969 January-December (Box 14, Folder 160-163)
      - 91st Congress, 2nd session: index, 1970 January-1971 (Box 14, Folder 164)
      - 91st Congress, 2nd session, 1970 January-1971 January 2 (Box 14, Folder 165-167)
      - 92nd Congress, 1st session: index, 1971 January-December (Box 14, Folder 168)
      - 92nd Congress, 1st session, 1971 January-December (Box 14, Folder 169-171)
      - 92nd Congress, 2nd session: index, 1972 January-November (Box 14, Folder 172)
      - 92nd Congress, 2nd session, 1972 January-November (Box 14, Folder 173-176)
      - 93rd Congress, 1st session: index, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 177)
      - 93rd Congress, 1st session, 1973 January-April (Box 14, Folder 178)
      - 93rd Congress, 1st session, 1973 May-December (Box 15, Folder 179-180)
      - 93rd Congress, 2nd session: index, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 181)
      - 93rd Congress, 2nd session, 1974 January-December (Box 15, Folder 182-184)
      - 94th Congress, 1st session: index, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 185)
      - 94th Congress, 1st session, 1975 January-December (Box 15, Folder 186-187)
      - 94th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1976 January- October (Box 15, Folder 188)
      - 94th Congress, 2nd session, 1976 January-October (Box 15, Folder 189-190)
      - 95th Congress, 1st session: index, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 191)
      - 95th Congress, 1st session, 1977 January-December (Box 15, Folder 192-193)
      - 95th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1978 January-November (Box 15, Folder 194)
      - 95th Congress, 2nd session, 1978 January-November (Box 15, Folder 195-196)
      - "Legislative Profile: prepared for William Moorhead for the period 1979 Jan. 15 - 1980 Dec. 31": Office of Legislative Information, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 197)
      - 96th Congress, 1st session: index, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 198)
      - 96th Congress, 1st session, 1979 January-July (Box 15, Folder 199)
      - 96th Congress, 1st session, 1979 July-October (Box 15, Folder 200)
      - 96th Congress, 1st session, 1979 November-December (Box 16, Folder 201)
      - 96th Congress, 2nd session: index, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 202)
      - 96th Congress, 2nd session, 1980 January-December (Box 16, Folder 203-204)
      - 96th Congress, 1st session: index on sythetic fuels, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 205)
        General
        See also: box 16, folder 202
      - 96th Congress, 1st/2nd sessions: synthetic fuels, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 206)
      - "Tributes to Congressman William S. Moorhead of Pennsylvania", 96th Congress, 2nd session, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 207)
      - Newsletters, 1960-1975, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 208-209)
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1956-1984; Series III; 2.25 linear feet (5 boxes)
  This series contains speeches and writings arranged chronologically. Detailed indices are included in the series.
  - Speeches, 1958 October 27 (Box 17, Folder 210)
  - Speeches: index, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 211)
  - Speeches, 1959 January- 1960 December (Box 17, Folder 212-214)
  - Speeches: index, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 215)
  - Speeches, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 216-217)
  - Speeches: index, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 218)
  - Speeches, 1963 January-November (Box 17, Folder 219-221)
  - Speeches: index, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Speeches, 1964 March-May 15-23, 1964 May 30-Jul, 1964 September-December (Box 17, Folder 223-227)
  - Speeches: index, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 228)
  - Speeches, 1965 January-May, August-October 17, 1965 October 20-November (Box 18, Folder 229-232)
  - Speeches: index, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Speeches, 1966 January-April 3, 1966 April 24-Jun, 1966 October-December (Box 18, Folder 234-236)
  - Speeches: index, 1967 February-December (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Speeches, 1967 February-Apr, 1967 June-December (Box 18, Folder 238-239)
  - Speeches: index, 1968 January-October (Box 19, Folder 240)
  - Speeches, 1968 January-May 11, 1968 May 17-October (Box 19, Folder 241-243)
  - Speeches: index, 1969 January-October (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Speeches, 1969 January-Mar, 1969 August-October (Box 19, Folder 245-246)
  - Speeches: index, 1970 February-December (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Speeches, 1970 February-December (Box 19, Folder 248-251)
  - Speeches: index, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - Speeches, 1971 January-December (Box 19, Folder 253-254)
  - Speeches: index, 1972 January-October (Box 20, Folder 255)
  - Speeches, 1972 January-Mar, 1972 April 8-16, 1972 April 20-May, 1972 July-October (Box 20, Folder 256-260)
  - Speeches: index, 1973 January-November (Box 20, Folder 261)
  - Speeches, 1973 January-November (Box 20, Folder 262-264)
  - Speeches: index, 1974 February-November (Box 20, Folder 265)
  - Speeches, 1974 February-Mar, 1974 June-November (Box 20, Folder 266-267)
  - Speeches: index, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 268)
  - Speeches, 1975 January-1976 (Box 20, Folder 269-270)
  - Speeches: index, 1977-1978 November (Box 21, Folder 271)
  - Speeches, 1977 January-1978 May, 1978 June-November (Box 21, Folder 272-274)
  - Speeches: index, 1979-1980 October (Box 21, Folder 275)
  - Speeches, 1979 January-1980 October (Box 21, Folder 276-278)
  - Speeches: index, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 279)
  - Speeches, 1981 January-1984 (Box 21, Folder 280-281)
  - Speeches on synthetic fuels: index, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 282)
  - Speeches on synthetic fuels, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 283)
  - Notes, n. d. (Box 21, Folder 284)
  - Writings (Box 21, Folder 284)
  - Articles with index, 1956-1967 (Box 21, Folder 285-286)
- MEMORABILIA, 1935-1988; Series IV; 13.0 linear feet (32 boxes)
  The files in this series are listed alphabetically. Within the files, materials are arranged chronologically. Oversize items are arranged at the end of the series.
  - Awards and certificates, 1944-1946, 1964-1976, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 287-289)
  - Calendars, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 290-295)
  - Calendars, 1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 296-302)
  - Calendars, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 303-307)
  - Calendars, 1966 January-1968 December (Box 26, Folder 308-315)
  - Calendars, 1969 January-Nov, 1970 January-1971 August (Box 27, Folder 316-323)
  - Calendars, 1971 September-1974 March (Box 28, Folder 324-331)
  - Calendars, 1974 April-1976 August (Box 29, Folder 332-338)
  - Calendars, 1976 September- 1978 May, 1978 April-December (Box 30, Folder 339-345)
  - Calendars, 1979 January-1980 November (Box 31, Folder 346-351)
  - Campaign materials, 1958-1968, 1970, 1972, 1974, 1976, 1978, n. d. (Box 32, Folder 352-357)
  - Campaign materials: recorded message with transcription, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 358)
  - Campaign materials of others, 1968, n. d. (Box 32, Folder 359)
  - Congressional memorabilia, n. d. (Box 32, Folder 360-361)
  - Diary, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 362)
  - Memorial citation and obituaries, 1987 August-Sep, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 363)
  - Photographs, family, [1924]-1979, n. d. (Box 33, Folder 364)
  - Photographs, 1957-1968 Jan, 1968 May-December (Box 33, Folder 365-371)
  - Photographs, 1969 January-April 28, 1969 May-1978 June (Box 34, Folder 372-379)
  - Photographs, 1978 July-1979 Apr, 1979 July-1981, n. d. (Box 35, Folder 380-388)
  - Photographs, n. d. (Box 36, Folder 389-395)
  - Presidential letter, pens, coin, 1964-1968 May (Box 37, Folder 396)
  - Presidential letter, pens, 1968 June-1975, 1977-1980, undated (Box 37, Folder 397-398)
  - Printed material, personal, 1935-1974, n. d. (Box 37, Folder 399)
  - Scrapbooks, 1958-1962 October (Box 38, Folder 400-409)
  - Scrapbooks, 1962 November-1965 December (Box 39, Folder 410-420)